Thursday, June 11th
Oh! And here's your big brother!
Sorry. Maaya said she wanted
to come see my new home.
I didn't have your cell number,
so I tried calling the home phone.
Ah, I was probably in the shower.
Also, I told Maaya that
you and I are siblings now.
I don't really min—
It sounds like she was watching when you
came over to talk to me during tennis.
And when you gave me the umbrella.
Sorry. I should've been more careful.
So...
can we exchange numbers?
Oh?
Good morning!
Good morning.
Why aren't you in bed?
I had trouble falling asleep.
Also, hey, Taichi-san said
he'd be leaving late today,
so I thought maybe we could all eat together.
I'll help.
Thank you.
It's been a while since we've
had breakfast together, huh?
Yeah.
Man, this is paradise.
Episode 3 "Reflection and Revision"
Don't be so dramatic!
Yum.
Hmm?
You're right! Yum!
Is this a rolled omelet?
A rolled omelet with broth.
With broth?
You add dashi broth when you make it.
Like the soup for noodles?
Well, we actually use white dashi.
Saki knows the recipe. Why don't
you make it for him next time?
I can't get mine this fluffy, though.
Oh, I like regular fried eggs, too.
Really?
Well, maybe I'll try if I'm in the mood.
Thank you for helping, Yuta-kun.
No trouble at all.
Oh, is it all right if I throw your
clothes in with this week's laundry?
That's kind of...
Actually, if you don't mind, Yuta-kun,
I'd be happy to do all the laundry myself.
What? No, I can't make you do that.
A lot of the fabrics are super delicate.
Do you know how to use a laundry bag?
Laundry bag?
It's made of mesh netting to
protect the clothes from damage.
Damage? Huh?
It's hard to explain, so we'll do it ourselves.
Oh, okay.
I'll wash Taichi-san's underwear.
Should I wash yours, too, Yuta-kun?
Huh?
Wait.
I'll go with you.
I apologize.
Huh?
I realize there's a possibility that
you prefer women's underwear.
It's not out of the question.
Huh?
Even though I've always
rejected rigid gender roles,
I just assumed you didn't know
how to do the laundry.
Ayase-san?
I've never seen you with
lipstick or foundation on,
but you might be the type who
only likes to doll up in private.
Hold on. Calm down for a second, Ayase-san.
Huh?
I've calmed down.
Okay.
Even if you're interested in cross-dressing,
it doesn't have to mean you actually do it.
I don't cross-dress, and I don't put
makeup on when no one's looking.
But your eyebrows are shaped really nicely.
Huh?
You must get them done, right?
Do you go to a salon?
A barber shop.
Huh? You mean your eyebrows
are totally natural?
Well, yeah.
I'm kind of jealous.
Don't you think it's hard to force all
sexual difference into just two categories?
Huh... Yeah, I guess so.
But earlier, in the moment,
that thought didn't even cross my mind.
I'm really not worried about it.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
But I can't forgive myself.
That's why I wanted to apologize.
Sometimes we do things reflexively.
Reflectively? Like light?
No, not that. I'm talking
about conditioned reflexes.
Oh...
I think sometimes you say or do things
on instinct and can't really help it.
I'm sure the ability to react reflexively
like that is useful in certain situations.
But still, prejudice leads to discrimination.
That's why we need to reexamine things.
Ayase-san, you've already reexamined
and reflected on what you did earlier.
Once you've done that, I don't think
you need to keep worrying about it.
Personally...
I don't think you're the type who can't
reflect on and learn from what you've done.
Ayase-san?
Asamura-kun, you really...
understand me too well.
All right, let's go!
You're already back.
What?
No, it's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Really?
Uh, I've got work today.
You were looking, weren't you?
So your eyes were drawn to
the hanging undergarments,
which is why, when I startled you,
you up and ran.
Did you think I might've thought you
were about to go in and steal them?
Well... I guess.
Even though they're your little sister's?
Well, yeah. I'm aware of that.
Sorry. That was a little unfair.
Huh?
Here. Have some cocoa.
Don't want it? I can take it back.
No, that's okay. I'll take it.
I guess this makes us even now.
Huh?
Your eyes being drawn to my underwear
is another kind of reflexive reaction.
But I don't think you're the type who can't
reflect on and learn from what you've done.
Well, that's a relief.
So does this mean my underwear was
tempting enough to you to catch your eye?
I didn't say that.
So it wasn't tempting at all? Huh.
Are you teasing me right now?
Oh, I wonder.
But you can't say the thought of stealing
my underwear didn't cross your mind, right?
I'd be lying if I said I didn't
feel any urge to take it,
but that doesn't mean I'd act on it.
Hmm. So you did feel an urge.
Having an urge to do something and acting
on that urge are two different things.
You're right.
Sorry. Let's drop it.
I've already eaten dinner and had my bath.
Huh? Oh, okay.
Goodnight.
Friday, June 12th
Hi, Big Brother.
Hey, not at school!
Did something happen to Saki?
Huh?
She's been like that since this morning.
You seem down. Did something happen?
Here it comes!
No.
Dad's catching the last train home.
Okay.
Sorry. I still haven't found a good,
high-paying job for you.
I never expected you to find one immediately.
But at this rate, you're going to be
making me dinner for nothing.
If you want me to help out more,
just say the word.
Sure.
Asamura-kun...
Are you willing to buy...
my body?
Asamura
Ayase
Sunday, June 7th
Sunday, June 7th.
I'm relieved, to be honest.
I could tell when we were introduced
that he wasn't a bad person.
And also that he's considerate.
He's the kind of guy who'll even draw
a fresh bath for me when he's done.
And I never expected
that he attended Suisei, too.
Monday, June 8th
Monday, June 8th.
Asamura-kun came and talked to me at school.
He's a lot more level-headed than I thought.
I'm a little annoyed that he believed
the rumors about me,
but I can't really blame him.
I know how people see me.
But he got mad, and recognized
that I was mad about it, too.
This might be the first time anyone has
understood my feelings so effortlessly.
Tuesday, June 9th
Tuesday, June 9th.
Memo: Asamura-kun likes
his fried eggs with soy sauce.
Today, I start cooking.
Asamura-kun is trying to find
a high-paying job for me,
so I feel like it's the least I can do.
He seemed apologetic when he told
me he hadn't found anything yet,
but I really didn't think it
would be that easy, you know?
The right way to depend on people, huh?
If I could do that, sure.
Wednesday, June 10th
Wednesday, June 10th.
I was listening to music.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention
I never thought he'd ask me...
English lessons?
I don't want him to see
What difference does it make?
how hard I actually work. I know it's not cool.
Maaya came to hang out at my new place.
The three of us played
games and laughed a lot.
I hadn't laughed so much in a long time.
We exchanged contact info.
Asamura-kun uses a landscape
photo as his profile picture.
Asamura Yuta
I'm not surprised.
Thursday, June 11th
Thursday, June 11th.
He said he wouldn't actually do it.
He said that having an urge and
acting on it are two different things.
I feel the exact same way.
I'm starting to realize that each and every
time Asamura-kun shares his thoughts,
it's always something that
I can relate to completely.
That's probably why this feels so right.
Asamura-kun is dangerous.
He understands me far too well.
Ayase-san, right now...
you're acting exactly like
the kind of girl I hate.
Using your looks as a weapon to get ahead...
I thought you didn't want to be seen that way.
If you can't prove people wrong in a way
that's not contingent on being a woman,
then what's the point?
But...
I felt like since you understand that much—
This isn't about me.
It's...
about you, Ayase-san.
I'm sorry.
Asamura
Ayase
I think my father used to be a really nice guy.
But after his company failed,
he stopped trusting people.
My mom started working
twice as hard to provide for me,
but he didn't seem to like that, either.
He'd say to her,
"You're nothing but a sex worker."
"You use your body to get customers."
Really degrading stuff.
I understand he was going through a lot,
but that didn't make it okay
to take it out on my mom.
I completely agree.
Huh?
Uh, well... that's kind of like
what happened to us, too.
After my mom cheated on my dad,
he became kind of paranoid
of women for a while.
Your dad did?
And maybe you did, too?
You and I have a lot in common.
Even the broken parts.
You might have a point.
But even with those parts, I have a feeling
we'll be able to get along all right.
As brother and sister.
Oh, hey. I don't mind if you want
to start calling me "big brother."
Thanks.
Ayase-san?
Let's make this work together, Asamura-kun.
Saturday, June 13th
Saturday, June 13th.
Asamura-kun and I ate dinner together.
Just the two of us.
We were able to convince our parents
to go out to eat for once.
It was actually Asamura-kun's idea.
He really is considerate of others.
That's exactly why I shouldn't
call him "big brother."
The moment I start calling him that,
I'll probably start depending
on him for everything.
I absolutely can't let myself do that.
I know it's strange to have toast with your rolled omelet with broth.
I'm sorry, Asamura-kun.
It isn't strange at all, Ayase-san.
I'm so glad.
But every time I call him "Asamura-kun,"
That looks great, Yuta.
Mind sharing with your old man?
I get this indescribable feeling in my chest.
One very different from the way
I'd feel calling him my brother.
I've never felt this way before.
I don't even know what to call it.
Before I knew it, I started to
have feelings for Asamura-kun.
My mind is in a haze.
Recently, even when I'm in bed,
I have trouble falling asleep.
And here I want live independently.
I'm getting so sick of myself.
What's happening to me?
Seriously...
Episode 4 "Tendencies and Strategies